

# Julio Cesar **Simental Ponce**

### ABOUT ME

I'm 34 years old, with 14 years of experience in web development.

I love photography, traveling and networking among the tech community.

I'm an easy going person, I like to work as part of a team and individually as well, with great ease of learning and continuous desire to improve my skills and be up-to-date on frontend technologies.

#### O CONTACT ME

Mobile +52 3333 688 399

@ Email julio@frontend.mx

A Location Colima, Colima, México.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sr. Frontend Developer & Tech Lead / Enroute / 2021 - currently - Remote from Colima, Colima, Mx

Sr. FrontEnd Developer / Price Travel / 2021 - 2021 - Remote from Colima, Colima, Mx

Sr. FrontEnd Developer / Roverpass / 2020 - 2021 - Remote from Colima, Colima, Mx

Sr. FrontEnd Developer / Cymatic (project) / 2020 - 2020 - Remote from Colima, Colima, Mx

Sr. FrontEnd Developer & Tech Lead / EB Digital / 2016 - 2019 - Remote

Software Engineer / Revenue.com / 2014 - 2017 - Remote

Software Engineer & CEO / 307networks / 2013 - 2014 - Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mx

Software Engineer & Tech Lead / Maushaus / 2011 - 2013 - Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mx

#### **EDUCATION**

TELEMATIC ENGINEERING / 2004 - 2008

TELEMATIC SCHOOL, UNIVERSITY OF COLIMA, MEXICO

INFORMATIC ENGINEERING / 2007 - 2008

SUPERIOR POLYTECHNIC SCHOOL, UNIVERSITY OF ALICANTE, SPAIN



